now what about how do you maintain the
level if gives daren't aren't you having
it is there a continuous flow of water
through here or is it a batch process if
you when you hook it up to the the
reservoir over here you can actually see
the level that you're at okay when I've
got it like this
I just know that I'm going to run it for
you no I'm just gonna pour in a gallon
and a half and let it go but if you have
a reservoir over here you can actually
raise the raise and lower the reservoir
and you'll see the line of the water and
you just adjust as just as you see
together you really want the water to be
right about the top of the plates maybe
just a little bit lower and that's fine
so with the reservoir it makes it very
easy so give us a step process number
one you put the water number two you put
the lid on is okay number one you take
your water whatever you want or you're
going to use whether it's gonna be
spring water if you're gonna be brave
and try a salt salt lake water or ocean
water your water or my water my elements
mix that all up together in a system
like this you're looking about it
yelling man they've been yelling a
quarter like I said you can put this in
a five-gallon bucket and that's really
easy okay my plates are sitting about
six inches off the bottom I know that
I'm gonna put in two and a half gallons
okay but make sure that your water find
out exactly how much you want pour that
in there and then actually you want to
seal this first because you can add your
water here so you want to seal this up
because this is not going to seal
properly if it gets wet and when you're
trying to get all these bolts that's why
actually they're all unequal so that
it's easier how much time do you have to
work with with that plumbers uh how long
does this setup you want you want us be
sealing it up
within about within less than 10 minutes
okay
I like I like to give it about five
minutes on a cool day I won't worry
about it too much but on a hot day I
want to seal it up within five minutes
okay and that includes putting the nuts
on yep well you you you put it in place
and then you just start tightening down
the nuts depending on on your mechanism
of sealing I actually told you with the
idea of putting a clamp on there
clamping it down and then tightening
down the nuts and that works too but you
know you you put it in place and that's
the first stage and then you tighten
down your nuts and you want all that
done within within 10 minutes okay and
then let's talk about filling up the
reservoir since we don't have the
reservoir to demonstrate here can you
can we use something just as a visual
okay so we're here and go to the bottom
go to the top
let's permit for the actually the
earlier portion where we're describing
the components let's describe the
reservoir okay
so as you can see the reservoir is
actually higher than the highest level
of this hydrogen device and there's
different ways to play with this and I
don't want to go into the mine eat a of
that because it really comes down to
personal preference but as you can see
filling up this device will bring you to
right about here okay and so what and so
you can actually see how much water you
have in your hydrogen device by the
level in your reservoir okay and so you
open that up pour it in fill it up to
there it equalizes it drops down you
fill it up again and and you're you're
fine any preferences on size of
reservoir you know it's it's totally
personal preference
these things are eight bucks apiece so
I've said hey can't argue with that I'm
just gonna buy them and put them in
place it's eight dollars so they're
fairly pretty cheap and not not
difficult to use and using the same
reservoir on this system over here yep
same deal
because I had a lot of them laying
around okay this is a safety bubbler
you're not gonna be running an engine
off of this thing well maybe you are if
you're running an engine off of this
thing you want to run it through a
safety bubbler right so let's just stick
with this scenario doing but let's now
pretend like this is your reservoir okay
for demonstration purposes so we're
going to run this bottom hose to the
bottom of this reservoir run the top
hose to the top of this reservoir and
we're going to look and see where the
level of our plates are compared to
where of course wants to on this on this
reservoir okay and so we're going to
fill up the reservoir to the level that
we that is indicated by where the plates
are so you're pouring the water into the
reservoir yes you're pouring the water
into the reservoir and you pour water
down into the reservoir and it will this
will equalize pretty quickly so
basically as fast as you can pour it in
it's going to flow in there and equalize
and when you reach the proper level
that's where you stop you can play
around with it the time I want to put a
mark on the outside of this just to be
sure right exactly and then also you're
gonna want to have some way to fasten
your reservoir in relation to the main
tank so that they're not moving back and
forth and right like on my in my video
presentation I had a picture of my
entire safety set up on the wall and
part of that was the reservoir yeah and
I feed this unit with that same
reservoir that I feed all my other
hydrogen movements so they're all daisy
chained together
so that's it's pretty simple okay so
that's that's the setup and I'm assuming
that people are just going to let this
let this hydrogen boil off into the air
if you're inside you want to run the
hose to the outside if you are letting
this sit outside you're fine you can you
can bubble it off through a through a
safety bubbler or something run into a
generator whatever your whatever your
preference is what if you are in the
alchemical process you're experimenting
and you've got some kind of a toxic
substance that you're replicating
then you would probably are you going to
have any of that coming out indeed what
you want is a if you're playing with
that stuff it's gonna be pretty advanced
but if you're playing with that stuff
you want to have multiple washes of
water now the other the other this this
container right here is the safety
bubbler and the wash okay and what
happens is the gas bubbles through there
and any particulates any any residual
from the machine is going to collect in
that in the second bubbler and what you
want if you're playing with toxic stuff
you want multiple stages of those so by
the time you get down here your gas is
completely cleaning you want them to be
tall too I use I use a harvelle clear
PVC pipes but caps on the end and bubble
gas through it because I can actually
see I'm a very visual person I can
actually see the bubbles and I can see
the gas escaping
I saw a $50,000 hydrogen prototype
destroyed in 10 minutes because he had
no visual feedback okay he relied
entirely upon computer gizmos and
gadgets to tell him what was going on
and one of them failed it was like a
China Syndrome a 25 cent piece failed
and a $50,000 prototype was destroyed
after 10 minutes very big fan of visual
feedback 1 bubbler would have told him
that something was wrong but he thought
but he was relying on a computer so
visual feedback on top of that and as I
mentioned in my lecture if you got a
long column of water and you're bubbling
hydrogen through it have fun with it put
a rodent coil around it see what happens
we're dealing with a with a practically
an electrolytic gas here yes
try energizing it with
with high frequency energies and such
there's one guy that was playing with us
back in the 60s and he would had a
little separator as the most inefficient
thing on the face of the planet but then
he'd run it between two eight inch
plates very similar to my lids there
he ran between two eight inch plates
that were separated about two inches
apart that would had a high-voltage
Corona in the center of it not enough to
not enough spark to ignite it but enough
but enough energy to turn that hydrogen
gas into DT Riemann he was running his
car on so play with columns shine lasers
through it shine ultraviolet lasers
through it do different stuff like that
and you'll start to see the quality of
gas change and start to see the
manifestation I
I swear someday we're going to see
somebody running a torch and they're
gonna start depositing gold on a piece
of steel and that'll be really cool so
that's the setup if you're working with
the experiment we're working with
elements like that you want to have
multiple stages just to make certain
that whatever you escaped off into the
air or what have you bleed off into the
air is going to be it's gonna be clean
what about the as you're running this
are you expecting the water level to
drop edit it's not going to drop super
fast since we're only producing like I
said this one's going twenty liters an
hour
there's your expansion ratio is at least
eighteen hundred to one
so 1800 liters is going to take a little
while to go through and that's burning
through one gallon of water but if
you're bleeding it off and taking your
minerals out that your video that you're
multiplying then you just you know keep
on adding water in proportion to the
minerals or the water that you've taken
out let's talk about harvesting minerals
and you've got this set up where you've
got the the reservoir and where where
the minerals showing up and that Ebola
the water that comes out of here and
collects in your reservoir and what
you're going to do there's a number of
different ways to work with that I would
suggest everybody get the book recovery
and process of precious metals by Bill
Amen because that is the definitive work
to me on how to recover elements from
any sin any situation whether it be an
oar or a deposit or whatever you're
working with
what's up Brian Ryan from oil well oh
you missed it yesterday I talked about
my oil well experience there oh I didn't
I didn't get back in time I didn't get
down time do we processed water from
three oil wells stripper wells the brine
was considered so strong but it was
hazardous waste and it had to be diluted
before it could be rejected really and
the wells produced maybe two barrels a
week 98 Brian did you ever do that
analyst analysis on the on the price I
got to I was able to smell out of the we
get your process okay and the waste that
precipitant we had worked with and I got
8 ounces of silver
Wow that's good stuff I love it
excellent sounds like a blast
yeah but the same thing it's a guy in
Denver you have to find a place to have
to find places to the process did you
you know this process to precipitate out
and drop out oh yeah we we ran up we
were pulling 20 amps we had an outdoor
tank they had to stuff in on the plates
in this cone-shaped
tank so we collect a collects
precipitated out afterwards and we would
run a place until the voltage went to
zip because the salt
well in this particular there was very
little cold and there was some platinum
but very little going going back to
known another affirmation of what's
going on here
yeah well that's that's the rot right
now there's nothing multiplying but
that's the dropping out so there we go
exactly we're actually part apart of
this element we missed the first part is
actually about multiplication of
elements - yes
which is which the hydrogen oxygen and
the energy is happening quite abundant
[Music]
say here's a smart man and working with
silver not that stupid could you could
you that's excellent now thank you and
you don't mind us including that in our
YouTube video here okay all right so I
need to get all these bolts that's why
actually they're all unequal so how much
time do you have to work with with that
plumbers uh how long does this set up
you want you want us to be sealing it up
within about within less than 10 minutes
okay I like I like to give it about five
minutes on a cool day I'll I won't worry
about it too much but on a hot day
I wanted to sue and you just adjust as
just as you see the death you really
want the water to be right about the top
of the plates maybe just a little bit
lower and that's fine
so with the reservoir it makes it very
easy so give us a step process number
one you put the water number two you put
the lid on is okay number one you take
your water whatever you want her you're
going to use whether it's going to be
spring water if you're going to be brave
and try a salt salt lake water or ocean
water your water or now what about how
do you maintain the level if gives
daren't aren't you having is there a
continuous flow of water through here or
you do set a batch process if you when
you hook it up to the the reservoir over
here you can actually see the level that
you're at okay when I've got it like
this I just know that I'm going to run
it for you know I'm just gonna pour in a
gallon and a half and let it go but if
you have a reservoir over here you can
actually raise the raise and lower the
reservoir and you'll see the line of the
water within five minutes okay and that
includes putting the nuts on yep well
you you put it in place and then you
just start tightening down the nuts
depending on on your mechanism of
sealing I actually told you with the
idea of putting a clamp on there
clamping it down and then tightening
down the nuts and that works too but you
know you you put it in place and that's
the first stage and then you tighten
down your nuts and you want all that
done within within ten minutes okay
and then let's talk about over my water
my elements mix that all up together in
a system like this you're looking at
about at yelling man we've been yelling
a quarter like I said you can put this
in a five-gallon bucket and that's
really easy okay my plates are sitting
about six inches off the bottom I know
that
going to put into an Afghans okay but
major us your water find out exactly how
much you want pour that in there and
then actually you want to seal this
first because you can add your water
here so you want to seal this up because
this is good not going to seal properly
if it gets wet and when you're around